{
    "API_KEY":"AIzaSyAMw1otSb1Tuh6Qe81Eo799bNSO55cqtTI",
    "SEARCH_ENGINE_ID":"59dddcc6d7ae4afdd",
    "OpenAi_Key":"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",
    "windowSize":5,
    "maxDocumentSize":10000,
    "relationType":
    [
        {"Relation":"schools_attended",
            "Subject": ["PERSON"],
            "Object":["ORGANIZATION"],
            "GPT3-Prompt": "Given a sentence, extract all instances of following relationship types as possible: SCHOOLS_ATTENDED WHERE SCHOOL IS EDUCATIONAL INSTITUTE. Output:[(PERSON,SCHOOl)] Sentence:"
        },
        {"Relation":"employee_of",
          "Subject": ["PERSON"],
          "Object":["ORGANIZATION"],
          "GPT3-Prompt": "Given a sentence, extract all instances of following relationship types as possible: Employee_of(SUCH THAT PERSON IS BEING EMPLOYED BY COMPANY OR PERSON WORKS AT COMPANY) . Output:Array of [(PERSON,COMPANY)] Sentence:"
        },
        {"Relation":"cities_of_residence",
            "Subject": ["PERSON"],
            "Object":["LOCATION", "CITY", "STATE_OR_PROVINCE","COUNTRY"],
            "GPT3-Prompt": "Given a sentence, extract all instances of following relationship types as possible: relationship type:  PERSON_LIVES_IN_LOCATION Output:Array of  [(PERSON,PLACE)] Sentence:"
        },
        {
        "Relation":"top_members/employees",
        "Subject": ["ORGANIZATION"],
        "Object":["PERSON"],
        "GPT3-Prompt": "Given a sentence, extract all instances of following relationship types as possible: relationship type: COMPANY_EMPLOYEE SUCH THAT COMPANY AND EMPLOYEE ARE NOUNOutput:Array of  [(ORGANIZATION,PERSON)] Sentence:"
        }
    ]
}